There you go. All done.
You're the best, Liz.
Thanks.
Sure. Anytime.
Hey, aren't you supposed to be
out hunting with the guild today?
Hmm. Yeah,
I had to take the day off cuz I sort of
have the same little meeting with someone,
oh!
I bet you have a little me, no?
it's not like that.
I have to get going.
I bet he must be pretty
special whoever he is, huh?
did you say something?
Get going!
It's rude to keep your date waiting.
It's not like
I wonder if I'll ever
find someone special.
but I'll be in love with a heart.
In my dreams I can't breathe.
When I'm on the body,
I'll be able to get rid of
This makes me feel like a weak person.
I wanna always be with you!
I'm giving everything I have.
Good enough, I guess.
I better get ready for the customers.
Perfect.
Welcome to Lizbeth's blacksmith shop.
Oh, hi.
Uh, I was wondering if
you do custom orders.
Hmm.
He doesn't look like
he has that much money.
I can.
The thing is, metal prices
are kinda high these days.
Oh, well, I'm not worried about the cost.
I just want the best sword you
can make as soon as possible.
Well, I make a lot of different swords,
but if you have any idea of the quality
of swords you want, I can make it.
Uh, sure. One sec.
So, I'm looking for something either
the same quality, or better than this.
An elucidator!
This is the gnarliest magic sword a
person can get from a monster drop.
What do you think?
How about this?
It's the best sword I ever forged.
I call it my masterpiece.
I don't know, it's a little light.
It should be.
I used a speed-type metal to forge it.
I'd like to test it if
it's cool. Test it how?
You know, it's durability.
What the heck are you doing?
If you break your sword,
I'm not responsible.
If it breaks, then that's too bad!
You broke my... masterpiece.
The hell were you thinking?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think yours
was gonna break so easy.
Honest.
Are you saying my sword, my masterpiece
of a sword was labor than you thought?
Yeah...
something like that.
For your information,
if I had the right materials,
I could make a buttload
of swords that would
shatter yours into a
million tiny little pieces.
You got that?
Oh, yeah?
That sounds like the kind
of sword I'm looking for.
As long as it can shatter mine, though.
Okay, smarty pants, but you have to
help me make it every step of the way.
Seriously?
Absolutely, and we'll start
by getting the medal for it.
I think I can handle that myself.
I'd rather not have you slowing me down.
Don't you dare insult me.
Believe it or not, I'm
an expert mace user.
Suit yourself?
So, where do we find the metal?
Floor 55 on the western mountain.
There's a dragon there that eats crystals.
According to the legends, it's supposed
to store a rare metal in its body.
Floor 55, huh?
Yeah, I should go alone.
And they say that in order to get the metal,
you need to bring a master smith along.
Still think going alone's a good idea?
I...
Fine, just keep quiet
and stay out of the way.
Keep quiet and...
By the way, my name's Kirito.
Looks like we're a party
until we make that sword.
Yeah, whatever, Kirito.
Well, if you're gonna be like
that, I can roll with it.
Liz-bet.
Hatsi!
It's cold.
Well, you should have
brought a coat or something.
I didn't know Floor 55 was
going to be this freaking cold.
Are you going to be okay without this?
You don't feel cold if you're disciplined.
If you're trying to piss
me off, it's working.
It's warm, though.
I can't believe I'm out here
all alone with this guy.
This is getting weird.
What's wrong, Lisbeth?
Giving up already?
Not on your life.
And if you're gonna be a jerk about
it, you might as well call me Liz.
Okay, okay.
Got it, Liz.
Yeah, well, don't wear it out!
It's beautiful!
What's your problem?
You should get your
teleport crystal ready.
I know, I know, I'm doing it.
And I'm handling this part on my own.
Once the dragon appears,
you're going to hide under one
of those crystals over there.
Don't come out no matter what.
Oh, come on!
I'm not a noob.
If I want to help you, I'll darn well...
Do what I say!
Good.
Hurry up and take cover! Okay!
Watch out!
It's a breath attack!
Wow, and with that
skinny sword, who is he?
Come on, stop playing with
it and finish it up already!
Damn it!
Don't come out yet!
What?
What's the big deal?
You've got it right where you...
Liz!
Hang on to me, Liz!
are we still alive yeah it looks like
it drink one of these just in case
Thank you, Eno, for...
for saving me It's a little
early to be thanking anyone.
We have to find a way to
get out of here first.
Huh?
Can't we just teleport out?
Teleport Lindis!
No way!
Well, if we can't use crystals, that
means there should be another way out.
How can you be so sure there is?
I mean, maybe this is some kind of trap
rig to kill anyone who falls into it.
Good point.
Maybe it is.
Would it kill you to at
least try to cheer me up?
I think I have an idea.
Really?
Yeah.
We could try rounding up the wall.
You're insane.
Maybe, but that's all I
got for ideas right now.
No way.
If I had more of a running start,
I probably would have made it.
Yeah, I don't think so.
This is kind of weird, isn't it?
This wouldn't happen in real life.
You know, going to strange places,
meeting a total stranger, and
then sleeping next to them.
I mean, you actually tried
running up that wall.
You really are a weirdo, you know that?
Well, excuse me.
Kirito, can I ask you something?
Ask away. I'm all ears.
Why did you risk your
life like that to save me?
I can't just sit back
and watch someone die.
I'd rather die alongside
him than do nothing.
Especially if that's someone's
a girl like you, Liz.
Wow, you really are an idiot!
You're the only person
who'd think like that.
Hey, hold my hand.
Kay.
It's so warm.
Huh?
Even though you and me are just these
ones and zeros in a virtual world.
I know.
What the?
What you doing?
Hmm? Here, look.
Is this what I think it is?
Uh-huh.
It's that special metal
we came all this way for.
Like you said, the dragon eats crystals,
and they turn to this in its stomach.
No wonder it's hard to find.
Yeah, but you found it.
What's it doing down here, though?
This hole isn't a trap like we thought.
It's the dragon's nest. R-really? Uh-huh.
And that's not just an ingot,
that's dragon excrement.
You know, poop. Huh?
Oh.
Ah!
Well, I guess this means we
got what we came here for.
Still stuck, though.
Wait, this is supposed to be
a dragon's nest, right? Yep.
Because dragons are nocturnal, so
it won't be long before it comes.
It's here!
What? What?
What are you doing?
No!
Hang on to me, Liz!
Almost there.
Wow!
Look at that!
Kirito!
You know what?
Know what?
Don't freak out!
But I'm falling in love with you!
I can't hear a thing!
What did you just say?
Never mind!
A one-handed longsword, right? Yup.
Make it awesome.
I didn't imagine it.
The warmth of Kirito's hands.
The way I feel.
As soon as I've made the best sword I can,
I'll tell him.
Whoa.
The sword is called Dark Repulsor.
One of a kind.
And it's not even in the
Infobroker's directory.
Go on, try it. Okay.
Good? Bad?
It's real heavy.
It's a good sword. Yay!
It feels like you forged
your soul into it.
Okay, you held up your end of the deal.
It's time for me to pay up, so how much?
Um, well, I don't really need any money.
Instead,
I'd like to be your exclusive
blacksmith from now on.
What do you mean? Exclusive?
What's wrong?
I mean.
Anytime you get back from the field, stop
by and let me do maintenance on your gear.
Every day.
From now till the end.
Liz I
Kirito
I just
I
Liz I was so worried
Asuna Liz Where were you last night?
I tried messaging you, but you didn't
answer and I couldn't track you on the map!
Sorry, I kinda got stuck
in a dungeon. A dungeon?
You went all by yourself?
Uh-uh.
I went with him.
Kirito?
Hey, Asuna.
Long time no see.
It's been what, like two days?
Well, this is a surprise.
I didn't know you wanted
to check this place out.
I wish you would have told me
I could have come with you.
I'm sort of confused.
Do you know each other?
Yeah, both of us are on
the assault team, so...
He said he was looking to
get a more powerful sword.
So I told him about you and your shop. Oh.
Why is she acting like that?
I swear, if you did
anything weird to her...
I didn't do anything.
Then why'd you stutter just now, huh?
You know, you could try to
show a little more compassion.
I almost got killed.
Like that's my fault!
Don't I always tell you not to fight Solo?
Right.
I get it now.
If this guy said anything
rude, you'd tell me, right?
Liz?
Do you want to talk about rude?
Try this.
First thing he does when he comes
in is shatter my best sword.
What? I'm sorry.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
He might be a little weird,
but he's not such a bad guy.
Don't screw this up, Asuna.
He's a keeper.
But I told you, it's not like that!
Liz?
Sorry, I have to go pick up some supplies.
I'll be right back.
But you're gonna leave the store?
Hold down the fort for me. Later! What?
No, wait, Liz!
Lisbeth.
I almost got away with it.
A couple more minutes,
and I would have gone back
to my usual cheerful self.
Liz, I...
How'd you know I was here?
I scanned the whole town
for you from up there.
Figures you'd do
something crazy like that.
Sorry if I worried you.
I'm fine now.
Must be all the excitement.
I'm not used to having adventures.
Anyway, I'll just forget
everything I said.
Okay?
Liz, I...
I just wanted to thank you.
See, I...
I don't know.
I always thought dying was better
than surviving day after day.
Living with the guilt.
Kirito.
But then, we got stuck in that hole, and
I was really happy we were still alive.
I realized that even here, our
lives are real and have meaning.
Thank you for helping me see that, Liz.
I guess it's what I've been
looking for this whole time.
Yeah, me too.
I know what you mean.
I was also looking for something.
Something real.
Hoping I'd find it.
The warmth of your hand.
For me, that was real.
Do me a favor, okay?
Tell us to know what you told me.
Liz.
I'm fine, really.
The getting over it part,
that's gonna take a while.
Until I do, promise me.
Promise me you'll put
an end to this world.
Till then, I'll keep doing what I do best.
I promise I will.
I swear I'll beat the game.
If you ever need your weapons or
gear repaired, my door's always open.
Sure.
Don't forget now.
You'll always be welcome at my shop.
Thank you.
Next time, the sword
dance of black and white.